算了，反正没有人想要吃鸡蛋
All right, so who needs eggs, anyway?
麦克，这是早餐
Mike, it's breakfast.
爸妈需要每天补充蛋白质
Mom and Dad need all the protein they can get.
你只会让我紧张，我再试一遍
You're just making me nervous. I'll try again.
好啊，12次后就会成功了
Hey, why not? The 12th time's a charm.
垃圾管道也有忍耐的限度
Even garbage disposals have limits, Carol.
我的碟子都放不下了
I got no more room on the tray, anyway.
爸妈能饱餐一顿了
Yeah, Mom and Dad are gonna scarf this stuff up.
-麦片？ -有了
- All right, we got oaties? - Check.
-花生酱加面包？ -有了
- Peanut butter toast? - Check.
-土豆片？ -有了
- Space bars? - Check.
-香槟 -有了
- Champagne? - Check.
洗胃工具？
Stomach pump?
凯罗，尽管说你的风凉话
Oh, sure, sure. Go ahead and criticize, Carol.
我和本准备早餐时你在干什么？
But where were you when Ben and I were planning this breakfast?
-梳妆 -你偷懒
- Putting on my face. - You missed.
好了
Okay.
我们应该开门踮脚进去
We're gonna open the door and tiptoe in without making a sound.
不，我们应该大叫大嚷
No. We'll scream and surprise them.
老年人受不了刺激
That could do serious harm to people their age.
那么你踮脚，我嚷嚷
So? You tiptoe, and I'll scream.
-本 -我喜欢嚷嚷
- Ben. - I like to scream.
你真走运
How lucky for you.
小声点，会吵醒他们的
Hey, come on, quiet down. You're gonna wake them up.
你们就不能理性一点吗？
Do I have to do all the thinking?
等我长大了.
Just wait till I grow bigger.
你永远也长不大
You're not going to grow bigger, Ben.
爸妈那天晚上还因此哭了呢
Mom and Dad were crying about it the other night.
好，准备好没？
All right. You guys ready?
结婚周年纪念快乐!
Happy anniversary!
-妈妈？ -爸爸？
- Mom? - Dad?
-奇了 -早上7点
- This is very strange. - It's 7:00 in the morning.
星期六早上，他们去哪了？
Saturday morning. Where could they be?
也许他们受够了我们，溜了
Well, maybe they finally had enough of us and moved.
这就像那部电视剧.
You know, this is exactly like that Twilight Zone I saw.
有一对夫妻 虽然大家都觉得他们怪怪的
There was these parents who everybody thought was just a little strange.
想不到一天夜里.
And then, one dark night...
孩子们跟踪他们进入一片阴森的树林
their kids followed them into this creepy forest...
接着看到奇形怪状的飞碟
where they saw them get into this weird-looking flying saucer.
他们发现父母原来是外星人
And that's when they found out that their parents were these aliens...
来自外太空
from outer space.
孩子们
Hi, guys.
结婚纪念日快乐!
Happy anniversary?
(English Subtitle) Growing.Pains.S01E19 -= The.Anniversary.That.Never.Was =- Subripped by zerox
这次准备好没？
You guys ready this time?
麦克，等等
Just a second, Mike.
-杰森？ -快点，盘子很重
- Jason? - Come on, these trays are heavy.
杰森，来吧
Jason, come on.
好的
Okay.
好了!
Ready!
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
真让人大吃一惊!
What a surprise!
待会看看厨房，都是垃圾.
Yeah, wait till you see the kitchen. There's garbage...
还有惊喜呢
Now for the rest of the surprise.
为了表达我们对父母的爱.
We wanted to give you something that reflects our love for you...
为了反映我们家庭的内聚力
and the deep bond that holds this family together.
-所以.. -我们要出城去
- So... - We're leaving town.
仅此一天，让你们摆脱我们
Just for the day, so you can spend it alone without any of us in your hair.
你们就别争辩了
Now, don't give us any arguments.
请你们别走
Oh, please don't go.
你们想得真周到
Oh, that's so sweet.
是的，可是爸爸妈妈今天都很忙
It really is, but your mom and I have a very busy day ahead.
我们打算今晚庆祝
We really planned on celebrating tonight.
奶奶来了
Grandma's here.
是吗？
She is?
奶奶要带我们去曼哈顿看
Yeah, Grandma's taking us to Manhattan for the matinee of La Cage Aux Folles.
这是本季度唯一值得观看的戏
Yeah, if there's one show you gotta see this season, this is the one.
妈妈!
Hi, Mom!
-真是个惊喜 -最好不过了
- Oh, guys, what a lovely surprise. - It's the best.
我约了一个病人 妈妈有篇报道要做调查
But I've got a patient to see, your mom has that story to research.
我们也许没时间在一起
We probably won't even have any time to spend alone.
你们犯不着冒生命的危险坐奶奶的车
So there's really no reason for you to endanger your lives in Grandma's car.
这份大礼要不要随便你们
You guys can use the gift or not. That's up to you.
我可不会错过能去纽约.
But I'm not going to miss my chance to see 24 of the hottest looking babes...
观摩那24位美女的机会
in the Big Apple.
我也是，不知道为什么
I'm with Mike. I have no idea why.
麦克，戏中那些“美女”其实是.
Mike, about these "hot babes" in the Cage Aux Folles...
爸爸.
Dad...
我已经告诉麦克关于那场戏的所有资料
I already told Mike everything he needs to know about the show.
滴水不漏，好了吗？
Everything. Got it?
麦克，希望有人告诉你.
Well, Mike, I hope someone has told you...
麦克，别忘了望远镜
Mike, don't forget your binoculars.
真是个好妹妹
Is this a great sis, or what?
凯罗，你不知道那些妞是男人扮的？
Carol, you do know that these hot babes are really guys?
我知道，但是.
Yeah, I do, but...
我们确实可以二人世界
You know, Jason, we could actually spend the day together.
是啊
Yeah.
遗憾的是我有一堆文案工作
Too bad I've got a mountain of paperwork to do today.
我也要去烫头发
I know, and I have a hair appointment...
还要花几个小时找资料
and several hours of research on the story I'm doing, but...
我可以推迟到明天
I could put those off till tomorrow.
星期六我要更新资料
But Saturday is my day to update the files.
还约了一个病人
And I do have that patient to see.
说得对
Oh, you're right.
懒洋洋的，放松的，没有人打扰的.
I guess I just got distracted by the thought of...
漫长的一天，会让我分神的
a long, lazy relaxing day together, with no interruptions.
而且
Besides...
我们一整天做些什么好？
what would we do all day?
很难说，清理浴缸吧
Oh, I don't know. We could always grout the bathtub.
我也可以像你一样取消工作
Well, I'll cancel my appointments if you cancel yours.
管道修理，工人今天会来修理垃圾管
The plumbing. The plumber's supposed to come by today to fix the garbage disposal.
害我担心呢
You had me worried there.
亲爱的，我们该走了，订座是午餐的
Honey, we have to go. That lunch reservation is for noon.
亲爱的，你在干嘛？
Honey, what are you doing?
清洁工要来了，不能让她看到这么乱
The cleaning woman's coming. I can't let her see this mess.
她早晚会发现我们是大懒虫
Sooner or later, she's bound to find out we're slobs, Maggie.
这下在海岸餐厅订了座.
Come on. For now, we have a reservation for lunch. Rockaway Beach.
我们去听涛去
Watching the waves caress the shore...
美酒金樽，合卺交杯
sipping champagne from silver goblets, and toasting the woman...
陪伴我靠运气，才智和美貌.
I was lucky enough to find...
才能娶来的娘子
smart enough to marry, and handsome enough to keep.
杰森，你有时候还真浪漫
Oh, Jason, you can be such a romantic sometimes.
暂停一下
Hold that thought.
你好
Hi.
我叫巴兹，是管道工
I'm Buzz, the plumber.
你们家垃圾通道坏了？
You got a bum garbage disposal?
我们取消了修理 你在车上没收到消息？
Gee, we cancelled that appointment. Didn't they call you in the truck?
车上没有对讲机
They won't let me have a radio in my truck.
我们有个约会得出去
Well, it's just that we have an appointment that we have to keep.
那我过一会再来
I could come back later.
谢谢
Thanks.
-等等 -等等
- Wait. - Wait.
你需要多长时间
How long would it take you to fix it?
半小时或45分钟
Oh, half hour, 45 minutes.
好吧，请进来
Okay. Come in, please.
我打电话去改订座
I'll call and move the reservation.
巴兹，维修费用怎么算？
Buzz, how much do you charge?
每小时50块
$50 an hour.
喂，弗瑞德，对
Hi. Oh, hello, Fred. Yeah.
好，等等 麦姬，你的编辑
Sure, just a second. Maggie, it's your editor.
喂？
Hello?
喂，弗瑞德
Oh, hi, Fred.
真的？
Really?
好极了
Oh, that's great.
今天？
Today?
可是我.
Oh, but l...
当然可以
Well, sure I can.
好的，好的
You bet. You bet. I'll be there.
对，谢谢，再见
Yes. Thank you. Bye.
我去通知饭店
Let me call the restaurant.
-杰森 -借电话一用
- Jason... - Can I have the phone?
-报馆弗瑞德打来了 -我知道
- That was Fred at the paper. - I know.
他肯定是打来祝贺我们的结婚纪念
I'll bet that nut called to wish us a happy anniversary.
杰森，你是要让我内疚吧？ 因为我有个坏消息
Jason, you're just trying to make me feel guilty because you know I have bad news.
对
Sure.
难道精神病专家也对付不了老婆？
What's the fun of being a psychiatrist if you can't play mind games on your wife?
亲爱的，我真的花了几个星期 才把采访定下来
Seriously, honey. I've been trying to nail down this interview for weeks...
可只能是今天
and it finally came through. But it's got to be today.
-好吧 -去华盛顿
- Okay. - In Washington.
华盛顿？
Washington?
采访谁？
Who with?
知道交通部长吗？
You know the Secretary of Transportation?
知道
Yeah.
我这次要采访副部长的.
I'm meeting with the third assistant to the deputy...
代言人的第三助理
of the undersecretary who reports to her.
哇
Wow.
老实说，这是我采访过最大的人物
Oh, honestly, honey, this is the only shot I'm going to get at this.
机不可失，时不再来
- And if I don't do it now, I've lost it. - Well...
飞去华盛顿要45分钟
It's a 45-minute commuter flight to Washington. I can go do the interview...
采访结束后我可以赶回来吃晚饭 我请客
and be back in time to have dinner with you. My treat.
若是你不满意.
But if you're disappointed...
我会留在家，吃午饭，我也会高兴
I'll stay home, I'll have lunch, I'll be happy...
-我也会很满足 -如果你一定要去.
- I'll be content, totally fulfilled... - Look, if you got to go...
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
我就知道父亲对你的看法是错误的
I knew my dad was wrong about you.
今天，我和你总会有机会.
Just so, at some point today, you and I finally get a chance...
去清理浴缸
to grout the tub.
肯定了
Count on it.
忘了带工具箱
I forgot my toolbox.
-再见，奶奶 -谢谢
- Bye, Grandma. See you soon. - Thanks a lot.
谢谢，奶奶
Thanks, Grandma.
她们的裙子真漂亮
I thought the gowns were beautiful.
这部戏有关的人员都应该枪毙
I think everyone connected with that show should be shot.
包括你喝彩的红头发姑娘？
Even the redhead you whistled at?
好像是莫里斯
That would be Maurice.
凯罗，这个笑话不错
Okay, Carol, it was a fine joke.
是个好笑话，甚至是好笑的笑话
A good joke. Possibly even a funny joke.
但受罪的人是谁？
But who really paid the price here?
是我？不，是分不清真假的本
Was it me? No. It was little, confused Ben.
莫里斯原来是爱荷华州的橄榄球员
Hey, you guys, Maurice was a tight end at Iowa State.
爸爸，妈妈，我们回来了
Mom, Dad? We're back.
迫不及待要告诉他们是吧？
You just can't wait to tell them, huh, Carol?
-爸爸妈妈？ -孩子们
- Mom? Dad? - Guys.
-今天很浪漫吧？ -不尽然
- Did you and Mom have a romantic day? - Well, not exactly.
你们小声点，我刚看完病人
Can you keep it down 'cause I'm just finishing up with a patient in here.
-好的 -妈妈在哪？
- Sure. - Hey, where's Mom?
华盛顿
Washington.
华盛顿？情况不妙
Washington? This is not a good sign.
也许是他们独处时，爸爸开起玩笑来
Hey, I bet when Mom and Dad got alone, Dad started telling his jokes...
妈妈就跳上飞机逃走了
and Mom hopped the first plane to anywhere.
麦克，有个死人躺在厨房里
Mike, there's a body on the kitchen floor.
男的女的？
Man or woman?
我再也分不清了
I can't tell anymore.
去看看是什么人
Somebody should go check him out.
本
Ben.
糟了，我的鸡汤
Look out. My chicken sauce.
-爸爸，你没看到.. -还好
- Dad, did you see... - Oh, good.
-没粘锅底 -爸，你没看到.
- It didn't stick. - Dad, you notice there's a...
-好看吗？ -好看
- So, how was Cage Aux Folles? - Great.
莫里斯还在剧团里？
Is Maurice still with the show?
-莫里斯 -你俩闭嘴
- Maurice. - Shut up, both of you.
-巴兹，怎样了？ -快修完了
- Buzz, how's it going? - Almost finished.
才修了5个半小时，1小时才50块
Only five and a half hours at $50 an hour.
爸，妈妈还回来吗？
Dad, is Mom ever coming back?
她说会赶回来烛光晚餐
She'll be back in plenty of time for our candlelit dinner for two.
晚上你们去奶奶家好吗？
You guys will spend the night at Grandma's, okay?
我们一天冒了几次生命危险了
Oh, come on, Dad. How many times do we have to risk our lives in a single day?
喂？
Hello?
亲爱的，非常非常对不起 我还在华盛顿
Oh, sweetheart. I am so, so sorry. I'm still in Washington.
一切都搞砸了
Everything got screwed up on this end...
采访推迟到明早
and the interview got put off until tomorrow...
今晚报馆让我在黄金饭店过夜
so the paper is putting me up at the Hotel Royale tonight.
明天一早就去采访
I'll interview him first thing in the morning.
然后我尽快赶回来庆祝咱的周年纪念
Then I'll get home as fast as I can to celebrate our anniversary...
真的，亲爱的，早知道这种情况.
because, I swear, honey, if I'd known this was gonna happen...
我就不会来了
I never would have come.
你是谁？
Who is this?
杰森
Jason.
修好了
All done.
好极了
Wonderful.
那.
So...
把帐单寄\给我吧
I guess you'll be sending me a bill on that.
特级邮递
Posthaste.
修理费总共多少？
How much will it come to?
劳务费加上.
Well, I have to add the labor...
-配件.. -大约多少？
- and the parts... - Ballpark?
347.75
$347.75.
好奇问句.
Just out of curiosity...
换个新的要多少钱？
how much would a new garbage disposal cost me?
好
Perfect.
你要换一个新的？
Would you like me to install one?
不，不，谢谢
No, no. No, thank you.
再见
Bye.
周年纪念快乐
Happy anniversary.
爸爸，这些垃圾你不吃了？
Hey, Dad, you gonna eat anymore of this junk on your plate?
-不，我不饿 -麦克.
- Nah, I'm not hungry. - Michael...
这叫鸡肉
it's fowl.
还真不知道
Tell me about it.
爸爸
Dad?
对不起，我没听见
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
可是你看上去是在听
Looked like you were. I guess you psychiatrists...
一直跟疯子打交道 练出一身装听的本事
get pretty used to faking it after all those years of listening to wackos.
“疯子”两个字对精神病医生来说.
Michael, "wacko" is a term psychiatrists reserve...
只能用在家人身上
for members of their immediate family.
-我说着玩的 -不要说着玩
- I'm just kidding. - Well, don't.
刚才所见乃经典的泄愤行为.
What you've just witnessed is a classic display of displaced anger...
我把一腔的怒气.
in which I allowed my frustrations to be vented...
发泄在第一个惹我的人身上
on the first available person to upset me.
这种行为缓解了我的精神压力
This transference lets me lessen my stress...
使我感到..自己很傻
and allows me to feel really stupid.
你不能就这样坐上飞机，一走了之
You can't get on that plane and leave.
-你爱的是我，你很清楚 -不，我爱的是拉里
- It's me you love. You know it is. - No, no, Curly. It's Larry.
-我一直爱着拉里 -可是你对我说的那些话.
- It's always been Larry. - But all those things you said.
是我弄错了，对不起
I was mistaken. I'm sorry, Curly.
我要跟拉里在一起
But my place is with Larry.
我不能留在这当你的陪亲
I can't stay here and be your stooge.
我会不择手段留住你
I'll do whatever I have to do to stop you.
我决不会让你上飞机
I'm not letting you get on that plane.
你当初就不该上飞机
You shouldn't have gotten on the plane.
对，722房西弗小姐
Yes, this is Mrs. Seaver in 722.
请帮我订一张飞机票
Is there anyone in the hotel that can help me with plane reservations?
有什么办法能让爸爸高兴起来？
I wish there was something we could do to cheer Dad up.
你离开家就行了
You could leave home.
-我有个主意 -麦克，爸爸是.
- I got an idea. - Mike, Dad's been deeply disappointed...
为了爱而失落
by the woman he loves.
经过莫里斯这一次，你肯定能体会
I'm sure you can understand that after Maurice.
-我这个是好主意 -失落是因为生了你
- It's a really good idea. - He's used to disappointment, Carol.
毕竟第一个孩子是你
After all, his second-oldest child is you.
不要太敏感了好不好？
You're really Mr. Sensitivity, you know?
这不止是一顿晚餐
It's not the dinner. It's just that...
他们需要在这个特别的日子.
they need at least a moment in that special day when...
情深地看着对方.
they can be together and look into each other's eyes...
回首过去走过的路
and think about the years they've shared.
幸福的岁月，艰难的岁月
The good times, the bad times.
他们要学戏里面的人？
You mean they want to "Do Wah Diddy"?
这20块是谁丢的？
Hey, who lost $20?
-什么？ -在哪？
- What? - Where?
这样你们就注意我了
Now that I have your attention...
爸爸干嘛不飞到华盛顿见妈妈？
why doesn't Dad fly to Washington and be with Mom tonight?
真气人，又被他想出来了
I hate it when he does that.
我去收拾行李
I'll pack him a bag.
我去订机票
I'll order the plane tickets.
一如既往，有功无赏
And I'll get no credit, as usual.
沃拉先生的自卑感.
And Mr. Walla is showing great improvement...
得到了很大的改善
in controlling his feelings of inadequacy.
心理治疗最大的用处是.
The sessions are proving especially useful...
减少结婚纪念日
in decreasing his anniversary.
删除“结婚纪念日”，口误
Ignore "anniversary." Freudian slip.
-减少焦虑 -爸爸
- In decreasing his anxiety. - Dad?
我在工作，删掉“我在工作”，儿子打扰
I'm working. Ignore "I'm working." Teenage son.
爸爸？
Dad?
我要关掉录音，不然在法庭上.
I'm turning the recorder off now, so as not to have it used against me...
这会对我不利
in a court of law.
什么事这么重要!
Mike, this better be important.
我代表大家说句，你走吧
Dad, on behalf of all of us, get out.
怎么了？
What's going on?
现在是你儿子跟你谈话
Come on, this is your son you're talking to here.
我察觉到今年的纪念日.
Now, I'm sensitive enough to know that this anniversary thing...
让你痛不欲生
has you feeling like garbage.
你直接刺他一刀好了
Why don't you just shoot him?
在你们伤害我以前.
Well, before anyone shoots me or shoves me down the garbage disposal...
而且这样也徒劳无功.
which probably doesn't work anyway...
我想知道为什么要走？ 为什么是本开车？
would you please explain to me where we're going? And why is Ben driving?
Well...
我想出来你应该飞去华盛顿 让妈妈吃一惊
I decided you should fly to Washington tonight and surprise Mom.
你想出来？
You decided?
这个主意不错，可是.
Well, that's a great idea, but l...
行李收拾好了，机票订了 奶奶正在赶过来
Dad, your bag's packed, your ticket's ordered, and Grandma's on her way over.
这个主意太好了，可是.
Oh, hey, look, that's wonderful, but I can't...
我就不能再留下了
stay here another second.
-爸爸，再见 -再见
- Bye, Dad. Bye-bye. - See you later.
“我解决了问题”？ “我想出来你应该飞去华盛顿”？
"I solved your problem?" "I decided you should fly to Washington?"
管他是谁的主意？你还小
Who cares whose idea it was? Grow up.
对，别老自以为是
Yeah. Stop thinking of yourself.
奶奶来了
Here comes Grandma.
不是奶奶，开这么慢
It's not Grandma. It's not going fast enough.
而且没有开到路中间
It's staying on the right side of the road.
-天哪.. -不是吧
- Holy... - Oh, no.
难以置信
I don't believe it.
-孩子们 -妈妈
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Mom.
-爸爸在客厅里吗？ -不在
- Oh, is your dad in the living room? - No.
很好，我要让他吃一惊
Good. I want to surprise him.
肯定会大吃一惊
And I think you will, too.
-在厨房？ -不
- Is he in the kitchen? - No.
-睡房？ -不
- In the bedroom? - No.
-他在哪？ -华盛顿
- Well, where is he? - Washington.
什么？
What?
我也不清楚，只知道是本的主意
I don't get it either. All I know is, it was Ben's idea.
飞往华盛顿的256航机马上就要起飞了
Attention. Final boarding, flight 256 for Washington National.
27号门
Gate 27.
旁边的座位没人，可以坐过去.
Maybe that aisle seat isn't taken if you wanted to slide over...
让大家多点空间.
then we'd both have more room to...
这是L排2座
No. This is Row L, Seat 2.
我的座位，风雨不改
This is my seat. All flights, any flight.
这是我的座位
My seat.
好吧
Okay.
借过
Excuse me.
-麻烦你.. -不行，这是L排2座，我的座位
- Do you mind if... - No. This is Row L, Seat 2. This is my seat.
风雨不改
All flights, any flight. My seat.
好吧
Okay.
-杰森.. -不，我叫路德
- Jason? - No. Luther.
我在跟他说话，亲爱的？
I'm talking to him. Honey?
-麦姬，怎么到这了？ -我想你
- Maggie. What are you doing here? - I missed you.
-我也想你 -太好了
- I missed you, too. - That's sweet.
你那个迫不及待的采访怎样了？
What about that big interview that couldn't wait?
我问自己，电视上的泰德.
Well, I asked myself what Ted Koppel would do...
若能嫁给你这种好男人，他会怎么做？
if he were married to a wonderful man like you.
首先是别让丈夫日夜操劳
Well, first of all, I wouldn't let him work that late every night.
今晚我应该陪我的大人物.
I figured I could fly back tomorrow to do the interview...
明早再飞回去采访
after I spend the evening with my main squeeze.
这么巧？
What a coincidence.
-你要去见什么人？ -一个非常特殊的人
- You're on your way to see someone, too? - Someone very special.
杰森.
Oh, Jason.
这个主意是你想出来的吗？
Did you think of this all by yourself?
这还多亏了你的另外几个男人.
Well, I got some help from the other men in your life...
麦克，本还有凯罗
Mike and Ben. And, not to mention Carol.
这是送给你的
Oh, look what I got for you. Look, these.
-玫瑰 -好
- Roses. - Yes.
亲爱的，真漂亮
Oh, honey, they're beautiful.
-我也有东西送你 -是吗？
- Oh, and I have something for you, too. - Yeah?
先生，谢谢
Sir? Thank you.
-对不起，你挡住我了 -对不起
- Excuse me. I can't see. - Oh, sorry.
亲爱的，我父亲没看错你
Oh, honey, my dad was right about you.
两个人度过了17个年头.
You know, when two people spend 17 years together...
我帮你吧
Can I help you with that?
好的
Sure.
17年值得我们二人.
I think 17 years deserves a moment alone together...
好好庆祝一下
just the two of us.
我们三人.
The three of us.
我们能情深款款地看着对方说.
So that we can stare into each other's eyes and say:
“若是可以重来..”
"If I had it to do over..."
“我还是会兴你度过这一切，我爱你”
Oh, honey, I'd do it all over again. I love you.
我也爱你
Oh, I love you, too.
我爱你们
And I love both of you.
-敬爱情 -敬爱情
- To love. - To love.
-我过得很愉快 -我过得很快乐
- I had a great time. - I had a wonderful time.
慢着，我希望再停留一秒钟
Wait. I just want it to last a moment longer.
不要再细数过去的事了
Well, then, let's not come back and say we did.
很好，但不了
Tempting, but no.
我们要回到孩子们身边
We have to get back to those three beautiful children...
他们想念我们，需要我们
who miss us and need us.
你这混蛋!
You little weasel!
嗨
Oh, hi.
-你死定了!嗨 -嗨
- You're a dead man, Ben! Hi. - Hi.
爱船返航了，待会见
Ooh, la, la. The Love Boat's in. Hey, I'll see you later, guys.
麦姬，知道我在想什么吗？
Maggie, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
-想什么？ -我想起了约吉.贝拉
- What are you thinking? - I'm thinking about Yogi Berra.
-这么巧 -他说过这么一句话.
- What a coincidence. - Well, it was Yogi who coined the phrase:
“没完的事情还没完”
"It ain't over till it's over."
[zeroxia@gmail.com] 2006.04.01